<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Pavel Naumov</title>
    <link>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Pavel Naumov</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/easy-fit/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/easy-fit/</guid>
      <description>EZ-FIT (EasyFit) Platform that would aggregate gyms, fitness studios, sports meetings venues. EZ-Fit would sell short-term memberships for the aggregated venues. Convenient mobile-first platform would provide fitness enthusiasts with easy and quick access to sports facilities.
In just a few clicks, the customer will be able to discover a variety of activities around them and buy a pass to the venue of their choice.
You can check it out at:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/influencer-app/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/influencer-app/</guid>
      <description>Influencer App A web-application that connects the influencers with potential clients. Clients can choose the influencer that fits their needs and create a job offer for them.
Creates opportunities for the influencers to be seen as well as for the clients to use influencers as means of marketing.
InfluenceMe</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/js-plus/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/js-plus/</guid>
      <description>JS Plus JS Plus is a start-up that helps doctors and clinics to avoid law infringements and possible customer extremisms. We provide our clients with all the document workflow (such as contracts, forms, waivers, agreements, etc.) that is required by law, thus protecting them from the possible issues that could have arisen.
I have created the web-application and currently maintaining the project with plans of creating mobile applications, too.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/stay-safe/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://pavel-naumov.herokuapp.com/projects/stay-safe/</guid>
      <description>StaySafe During the summer of 2017, Portugal has experienced several dangerous fire fires that took lives of 100+ people. StaySafe attempted to impact this situation by showing people the impacted area, the safe route and notify people around if there is something happening.
StaySafe is a web-application that helps you and your family to be aware if your state and location during dangerous events. It would notify you and your family if there is a hazardous event near you, and provide further instructions regarding the situation.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>